(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T08:31:23.333243",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
本日は鷹嶺ルイ3Dお披露目配信にご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending Takane Lui's 3D reveal stream today.
この配信はいたって、そう、いたって健全ですので、ご家族、お子様連れ、そして友達同士、
This stream is extremely, yes, extremely wholesome, so please enjoy it with your family, children, friends,
いる方は恋人同士でお楽しみください。いない方は……そうですね。
and if you have one, your lover. If you don't... well.
えー、一人でぶち上がっていきましょう！盛り上がっていけるかー！？
Let's get hyped all by ourselves! Can we get hyped?!
うん、みんな盛り上がってるね！いい感じ。
Yeah, everyone's getting into it! Looking good.
ということで、開始までもうしばらくお待ちください。
With that said, please wait just a little longer until it starts.
「俺んことここないか？」
"Wanna come back to my place?"
ワンナイト・カニバル 胸の奥 zuki-zuki と鳴ってる angel
One night carnival, my heart's beating so loud, angel
「とにかくもう行儀良く真面目なんてうんざりだった」 angel
"Anyway, I was sick of being serious and well-mannered," angel
俺んとこ こないか？
Wanna come back to my place?
退屈に怯えてたのさ
I was terrified of the boredom,
夜の闇に逃げ込んだ angel
escaping into the darkness of the night, angel.
俺たちまるで
We were just like...
捨て猫みたい
like stray cats.
Can you master baby? master baby!
Can't you master baby? master baby!
Can't you master baby? so long...
瞬きもせずに
Without blinking,
俺達は光の渦に巻き込まれてく
we're sucked into a swirling light.
雲の隙間に
In between the clouds,
青白き月よ 照らし出せ
shine on, blue-white moon.
星が瞬く distance
The stars twinkle in the distance.
さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
We're legendary loners.
One Night Carnival fun fun
風に香る tactics が俺の胸を締め付ける angel
The fragrance of tactics on the wind makes my heart clench, angel.
Can you master baby? master baby!
あの頃の俺達、闇の中じゃなくちゃ夢見られなかった
Back then we couldn't dream except in the dark...
あのミラーボールみたいに明るくて真丸なお月様に憧れただけさ
...we just wanted to be like the moon, bright and round as a mirrorball.
行こうぜピリオドの向こうへ
Let's go to the other side of the period...
恋をしているのさ この夜に恋をしているのさ
I'm in love, I'm in love with the night.
やがて海が見える さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
Soon we'll be able to see the ocean. We're legendary loners.
今だけは 悲しい歌 聞きたくないよ
Right now, I don't want to hear any sad songs.
Can you master baby? master baby!
Can't you master baby? master baby!
Can you master baby? be my baby!
Can't you master baby? so long so long...
One Night Carnival fun fun
俺たちが情けなかったことに出会いなんかなかったよ、ただ少しだけ不器用だったのかも知れない
There wasn't any reason for our sulking... maybe we were just a little clumsy.
恋をしているのさ この夜に恋をしているのさ
I'm in love, I'm in love with the night.
やがて海が見える さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
Soon we'll be able to see the ocean. We're legendary loners.
One Night Carnival fun fun
あの頃の俺たち 闇の中じゃなきゃ夢見られなかった
Back then we couldn't dream except in the dark.
あのミラーボールみたいに明るくて 真丸なお月に憧れただけだ
We just wanted to be like the moon, bright and round as a mirrorball.
行こうぜ、ピリオドの向こうへ
Let's go to the other side of the period...
もうすぐ海が見える
We can almost see the ocean.
さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
We're legendary loners.
One Night Carnival fun fun
One Night Carnival... Let's get free
廃退して 捨てられない夢 妬み 憂い 嫌い返して
It's grown old so I can't throw it away, I envy and grieve my dream, and hate it which hates me.
彷徨して 捨てられない君 私 誰 誰か愛して
It keeps loitering so I can't throw it away. Who are you? Am I? Someone please love me.
ビビ デビビ デバッド
Bibi de bibi de baddo
抱きしめてラブ
Hold me tight love,
見せかけたラブ
feigned love...
廃れて 捨てられない
Worn out and unable to be thrown away,
嫉まれ 憂い 嫌い 返して
I envy, grieve, and throw the hatred back.
出てこないでララ
Don't come out, la la...
妖しげならラ
...suspiciously, la la.
廃れて 捨てられない
Worn out and unable to be thrown away,
憧れてない
not even longing for it,
廃れて 捨てられない
worn out and unable to be thrown away,
消えかけたララ
fading away, la la...
あなたのそばで
...right by your side.
赤い糸 絡まりも連れて
Tangled up in the red string of fate,
浅い心も ざまくらかして
making a mockery of even my shallow heart,
泣き頭隠していくんだ
I go on, concealing my crying face.
存在私は くだらぬ馬鹿商売
My existence is just a foolish business.
ビビデ ビビデ バット
Bibide bibide bad...
...bibide bibide bad...
ビビデ ビビデ バット
...bibide bibide bad.
鮮やかなララ
A vivid la la...
目障りならラ
...an unsightly la la.
無慈悲でもない 痛みなどない
Merciless, painless,
死ねばよかったララ
I should've just died, la la...
出てこないでララ
...don't come out, la la.
偽善者のララ
A hypocrite's la la...
情けないなどない 嫉火だらけなんだ
no pathos, full of jealousy.
死ねばよかったララ
I should've just died, la la...
あなたのそばで
...right by your side.
はい、というね 3Dお披露目ね
Yes, so... this 3D reveal debut...
ホロライブ 女... あ ほら、ホロライブ
HoloLive wom... Ah, HoloLive...
6期生 ホロックスの女幹部 鷹嶺ルイと申します。 ついに、3Dになりました！
6th generation, HoloX's female executive, Takane Lui! Finally, I'm in 3D!
どう? 私のスタイル。
How is it? My style.
全身で見てどうですか?
How does it look in full body?
美しいでしょ?
Isn't it beautiful?
みんなもね、美しいって言ってくれてますね。よかったー！
Everyone's saying it's beautiful, too. I'm so glad!
はい、ということで 2曲ね続けてお届けさせていただいたんですけれども、
Yes, so we continued by delivering two songs,
最初はみんなね、これでするんじゃないかって思ってたんじゃないですかね、ワンナイトカーニバル。
but wasn't everyone thinking we'd start with this? "One Night Carnival."
こちらはね、もう気付いてる人もいたんですけど、ホロックスのみんなにコーラスをしてもらいました。
As for this one, some people already noticed, but I had all the HoloX members do the chorus.
気付いた? 気付いたかな?
Did you notice? Did you notice?
はい、ということで、初配信のね、リベンジを今日させていただきました。全部ね、マネちゃんに怒られずに歌うことができました！
Yes, so today I got my revenge for my first stream. I was able to sing everything without getting scolded by manager-chan!
ぽちぽちぽちぽちぽちぽちぽちぽち...
Yay, yay, yay, yay...
ということで、あ、そういえば、こっちか。 ハッシュタグ 鷹嶺ルイ3Dでね、先ほどの、ま、くそ、コラ感、
And by the way, oh right, over here. With the hashtag Takane Lui 3D, earlier... well, damn, photoshop-like...
クソコラ感満載のワンナイトカーニバルの お写真だったりとか、
photos of One Night Carnival full of bad photoshop, or...
ちょっとね、かっこいいミーラの、 ミーラ最終的にホークアイになったの、見ましたか?
did you see Mira finally becoming Hawkeye?
そういった写真を どんどんね、鷹嶺ルイ3Dで つぶやいてくださると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you keep tweeting photos like that with Takane Lui 3D.
たくさんつぶやいて私をトレンド1位にしてください。よろしく！
Please tweet a lot and make me #1 on trending. Thanks!
ということで、ホークアイね、見たいって言ってる人がいたので、
So, since someone said they wanted to see Hawkeye,
ホークアイちょっとやってみるか。
I'll try doing Hawkeye.
できるかな? んぱー！
Can I do it? Npar!
おおー！
Ooh!
そこにいる! チャンネル登録してないきみ!
You over there! You who hasn't subscribed!
チャンネル登録してないけど ちょっと、3Dだから見てみようかなっていう あなた!
You who hasn't subscribed, but thought "since it's in 3D I'll take a look"... you!
はい、今すぐチャンネル登録ポチッて押してください! はい、お、押すよね?
Yes, click the subscribe button right now! Yes, you'll press it, right?
はい。 ルイーズブリタニアが命じてるよ!
Yes. Louise Britannia is ordering you!
ということで、チャンネル登録みなさんよろしくお願いします！
With that said, everyone, please subscribe to the channel!
はい、ということで、そういえばこのステージ、いかがですか? ちょっと月明かりがね、すごく綺麗で、
Yes, so, speaking of which, how is this stage? The moonlight is so pretty,
あの、ちょっとワンナイトカーニバルでまんまるなお月さんって言ってるけど、三日月つってね、
and well, saying it's a round moon in One Night Carnival, but it's a crescent moon...
まんまるじゃねえじゃんつってね、これ、これ気づいた人いるかな? なんか、ちょっと任務の場所みたいじゃないですか。たか、
saying it's not round at all, I wonder if anyone noticed this? It looks kind of like a mission location. Taka...
うん、私、たか、ま、たかなので、 こういったね、森に結構、ちょっと行ったりとかするんですけど、
um, I'm Taka, well, I'm Takanene, so I often go to forests like this,
ホロックスの任務とかもよくここで待ち合わせとかをするので、こういったセットを作っていただきました。どうですか?
and HoloX missions often have meetups here, so they made a set like this. How is it?
めちゃくちゃおしゃれでしょ?
Isn't it super stylish?
うん、あとね、なんか、ホロライブの先輩方にもぜひこのステージ使ってもらいたいなっていうことで、はい、このステージを作っていただきました。
Yeah, and also, I'd really love for HoloLive's seniors to use this stage too, so yes, they made this stage for me.
おしゃれでしょ おしゃれ おしゃれ
Stylish, right? Stylish, stylish!
ということで、あ、そういえば私ののお披露目は終わったんですけど
And so, oh, speaking of which, my debut stream is over, but...
もう1匹お忘れじゃないですか？
aren't you forgetting one more member?
ねぇ、ツクネとツミレちゃんはお披露目ね、先にさせていただきましたが、あいつのこと忘れてませんか？
Tsukune and Sumire already had their debut first, but aren't you forgetting someone else?
うんうん、あ、みんなわかるかな？
Hmm hmm. Ah, does everyone know?
じゃあみんなで呼んでみましょうか、あいつ！寝てないかな大丈夫かな？
Let's call him together, shall we? Is he sleeping? Will he be okay?
はい、ということで、ガンモー！
Alright, with that said... Ganmo!
おお、来た、飛んできた！
Oh, he's here! He flew in!
いや、ガンモめちゃくちゃかわいいでしょ！皆さんにご挨拶
I mean, Ganmo is ridiculously cute, right? Go ahead and greet everyone.
はい、ということで私の腕に止まれるか？止まって見せてくれ。
Alright, so can you land on my arm? Show me you can land on it.
ガンモ、お？
Ganmo? Oh?
ああ！いい子ですね！止まれた止まれた。
Ah! Such a good boy! You landed! You landed!
じゃあね、今夜はお酒をあげよう。お酒飲んでよし。うん、いい子だ。
Well then, tonight I'll treat you to some alcohol. Drink up. Yep, good boy.
あれ？ていうか、そもそもあの杖どこやったの？杖どこやってきた？杖、杖あるのかな？
Huh? Wait, come to think of it, where did you put that staff? Where did you bring the staff from? Is there a staff?
なんかさ、私の今回のサムネに杖あったと思うんですけど、今ね、杖がないんですよ。ちゃんと持って、あ！
You know, I think my thumbnail this time had a staff in it, but right now, there's no staff. Holding it properly—ah!
あれ？あ！ど、どういう仕組みそれ？浮いてる、あ！
Huh? Ah! Wh-What kind of mechanism is that? It's floating—ah!
ちゃんと掴んで持ってきてくれたのね。ありがとう！
You grabbed it and brought it over properly. Thank you!
いやガンモめちゃめちゃかわいい。
Man, Ganmo is super cute.
ツクネとね、ツミレもちゃんとセットでね。
Tsukune and Sumire are properly here as a set, too.
ほら見てください、このユレカン。
Look at this wobbliness!
かわいいね、ちゃんと上目遣いしてますね、ガンモ。
So cute, Ganmo is looking up at us properly.
あれ？何？あら、そういえばワンナイトカーニバルの時出てこなかったもんね、君。
Huh? What? Oh, come to think of it, you didn't appear during One Night Carnival, did you?
あ、じゃあちょっと私もサングラスつけさせてもらって、ちょっと
Ah, well then, let me put on some sunglasses too, and...
お, じゃあ一緒に写真でも撮る？こうかな？
Oh, shall we take a picture together then? Like this?
はい、チーズ。あ、どう、どう、どう？撮れた？うん。
Say cheese. Ah, how, how, how is it? Did you get it? Yep.
はい。ということでワンナイトカーニバル、そしてミラとね、歌わさせていただきましたが、この配信のサブテーマ、実はあるんですよ。
Right. So we sang One Night Carnival and Mira, but this stream actually has a sub-theme.
タイトルにもあります、鷹嶺ルイ 成長の奇跡、というね、ちょっと、このサングラスつけて言うことじゃないんだけど。
As the title says, "Takane Lui's Miracle of Growth," though maybe not while wearing these sunglasses.
ちょっ、さ、サングラス取るか？ちょっとサングラス取ろう。取って、よっこいしょ。はい、ということで、
Hold on, should I take off the sunglasses? Let's take off the sunglasses. Take them off, heave-ho. There, so...
ちょっとエモいこと言うのにあのサングラスだとね、ちゃんとか、私が笑っちゃうから。
Saying something emotional while wearing those sunglasses makes me laugh.
ということでサブテーマ、鷹嶺ルイの成長の奇跡ということでね、えー、私がデビューして半月ちょっと、まあ半少し以上ね、あの活動してきたんですが、その成長の奇跡を皆さんと一緒にちょっと振り返っていきたいなっていうことと、
So for the sub-theme, "Takane Lui's Miracle of Growth," um, I've been active for a little over half a month, well, slightly more than half a year since my debut, and I want to look back on that miracle of growth together with everyone,
あと私やっぱり歌が大好きで、歌を頑張っていきたいなっていう願いも込めて、ちょっと歌中心のね、お披露目をさせていただければなと思いますので、最後まで楽しんでいってください。
and also, because I really love singing and want to work hard at singing, I hope to make this a debut centered around singing. Please enjoy it all the way to the end!
ちょっと水だけ飲んでもいいですか？水だけ飲みますね、ちょっと待ってください。
May I just have some water? I'll just drink some water, please wait a moment.
ということで、えー、続いての曲いきましょうか。続いての曲は皆さんも結構記憶に新しいんじゃないでしょうか。この曲聴いてください。プロローグ。
And with that, um, let's move on to the next song. The next song is probably pretty fresh in everyone's memories, isn't it? Please listen to this song. Prologue.
目にかかる髪の毛とかき分けた指
Hair falling over my eyes, and fingers brushing it aside
壊れそうどこか寂しげな背中
A back that looked fragile and somehow lonely
頼りない太陽を滲ませながら
As the unreliable sun blurred before my eyes
微笑んだその横顔見つめていた
I gazed at your smiling profile
キミに触れた時
When our fingers intertwined,
高鳴る鼓動が聞こえた
I heard the echoing beat of a heart.
初めて知ったの
For the first time, I realized
思いは力になって
that feelings can become strength.
...
(Instrumental)
あなたを探してる
I look for you,
隠した瞳の奥で
closing my eyes tightly.
誰にも見えぬように
With nowhere else to go,
行き場もなくて
wandering around,
さまよいながら あなたと見る世界は いつでも綺麗だった
the world with you is always beautiful.
空には一つだけ 儚く光る 小さな星を残してる
In the sky, there is only one faint ray of light.
...
(Instrumental)
求めては突き放す
Even if I search,
読めない心
I can't put my feelings into words.
見つめられれば ほどに嘘がつけない
I cannot hide how much it hurts.
力なく点滅する あの痛みを
I looked up at that fading pain,
見上げていた その横顔は優しかった
but your face was so gentle.
破れそうに膨らんで
Swollen as if ready to burst,
真っ赤に熟れた果実は
the crimson fruit is...
誰かの紡手を待っているね
waiting for someone's hand.
それは私だった
"That was me," I whispered.
あなたがあふれてく 抑えた胸の数だけ隠さない
You overflowed and held back just the beat of my chest,
始まりを
wanting it to start hiding.
次から次へ 手の平に伝わっていくよ
From now on, touching the palms of our hands...
風は冷たいのに
Even though the wind is cold,
そんな心は赤いままで あなたに触れたいと思ってしまったどうして
my heart is still red, and I regret wishing to touch you.
二人であったの
We were together.
痛くて苦しくって それなら
If it hurts so much that I want to die,
見えないように どこかへ飛んでゆけ
I hope it becomes invisible and flies away somewhere.
...
(Instrumental)
そんなものにあなたを探している 何度も
Even so, I search for you again and again,
名前を呼んで
calling your name.
空には一つだけ 儚く光る 小さな星を浮かべて
In the sky, a single small star is floating, faintly shining.
...
(Instrumental)
キミに触れたとき 高鳴る鼓動が聞こえた
The sound of a heartbeat echoes when I touch you.
長い長い夜を超えて
Crossing a long, long night,
泣いて枯れてまた泣いて
crying, withering, crying again,
君へ届きと願う 私の歌
my song wishing to reach you.
聞こえますか
Can you hear it?
I love you...
最後に言えずにいた
What I couldn't say in the end,
今更だけど伝えたい
though it's too late, I want to tell you—
思いが叶う 愛してる何度も
feelings come true. I love you, over and over,
何度でも聞いて欲しい 君を愛してるから
I want you to hear it again and again, because I love you.
守るものなんて何もないはずだったのに
I thought there was nothing left to protect,
君の存在が私を臆病にさせた
but your existence made me cowardly.
君の存在が
Your existence
私を臆病にさせた
made me cowardly.
なくした気持ちが少しずつ戻り
The lost feelings slowly returned,
初めて来て こういうんだ
and coming here for the first time, feeling this way...
二人ならきっと...
If it's the two of us, surely...
I love you...
最後に言えずにいた
What I couldn't say in the end,
勇気を出して伝えたい 思いが叶う
gathering the courage to tell you, feelings come true.
I love you だから何度でも
I love you, so over and over,
キスをしよう君を
let's share a kiss, you and I.
愛してるから
Because I love you...
さよなら顔を教えてく冷たさ
Saying goodbye, the coldness teaching me...
二人巡り会えた
That the two of us meeting
それって奇跡
was a miracle.
なんてね きっと
Or so I'm sure...
I love you...
最後に君に
To you, at last,
こうして二人肩を寄せ合っていられるうちに
while we can still lean on each other's shoulders like this,
I love you 何度も何度でも伝わるまで君を
I love you, over and over, until it reaches you—
愛してる
I love you.
さよなら また会える こうして二人
Goodbye, we'll meet again, the two of us doing this.
いつの日か果て目を閉じれば思いだせるよ
Someday when it ends, if I close my eyes, I can remember.
I love you だから もう二度と振り向かない君と
I love you, so with you who will never look back again,
そばにいるから
I'll be by your side.
君を愛してる...
I love you...
大変申し訳ございません。こちらわね、あの弁明させていただきますんで...
I am terribly sorry. As for this, um, I will explain myself...
申し訳ございません、怒らないでください。
I'm so sorry, please don't get mad.
本当に、本当にごめんなさい。
Really, I'm truly sorry.
本当にごめんなさい。えっ？
I'm really sorry. Eh?
禁酒？えっ、禁酒はちょっと、あの...毛が重くないですかね？
Prohibition? Eh, prohibition is a bit... wouldn't that be too heavy?
ちょっとそこは、酒なしじゃ生きてけないのよ！
Wait, without alcohol I can't live!
頼みます、お願います！許して、許して！
Please, I'm begging you! Forgive me, forgive me!
痛い、痛い！
Ouch, ouch!
いた！痛い！やめろ、やめろ！
Ouch! Ow! Stop it, stop it!
やめろ！やめろ！やめろ！
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
痛いよぉ！
That hurts!
許してよぉ……ぐわあ！
Forgive me... Gwah!
どうしよう……
What should I do...
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
はい、もう一つのステージは、このバーステージです！
Yes, the next stage is this bar stage!
いや、このバーステージ、めちゃくちゃおしゃれじゃない？
Man, isn't this bar stage super stylish?
おしゃれでしょ？なんか私らしくて。
It's stylish, right? Kind of suits me.
私のね、あの、イメージカラーであるワインレッドをね、基調としたバーを作っていただきました！
They made a bar for me based on my image color, wine red!
実はね、このバー、いろんなね、仕掛けというかステージに分かれてるんですよ。
Actually, this bar is divided into various gimmicks, I mean stages.
3つのステージに分かれてるので、いまね、こちら紹介したいと思います。
It's split into three stages, so I'd like to introduce them now.
まずは後ろに見えるのが、バーですね。バーステージだからバーあるんだけど（笑）
First, what you see in the back is the bar. Well, it's a bar stage so there's a bar (laughs).
バーね、はい。結構ね、こちらでお酒を飲んだりとか、
A bar, yes. People can drink alcohol here,
まあ、ホロックスが経営しているバーなので、ちょっとお会計はね、あのどのくらいになるかちょっと保証はできませんけれども、みなさんでね、ぜひぜひお酒を飲み来していただければなと、思います。はい。
Well, since it's a bar run by Holox, I can't guarantee how much the bill will come to, but I hope you'll all come and have a drink! Yes.
そして、こちら真ん中のステージは、椅子だったりね、ソファだったりがあるおしゃれな、まあ観客席というか、お酒を飲むスペースになってます。
And then, this middle stage has chairs and sofas—it's a stylish viewing area, or rather, a space for drinking alcohol.
で、このね、スペースめちゃくちゃすごいんだけど、見えるかな？こっちかな？こっちに行くと、じゃーん！絵画が飾ってあるんですね。
And this space is super amazing, can you see? Over here? If you go this way, ta-da! Paintings are on display.
いや、これすごくない？いいね、おめでとうおしゃれ！おしゃれでしょ？
Wow, isn't this amazing? Nice, congrats, stylish! Stylish, right?
これね、椅子をどけたりとかテーブルをどけて、あの、このね、バッグで踊ったりとかしたらカッコいいんじゃないかなと思って、
I thought it would look cool if we moved the chairs and tables and danced with this background,
ちょっと、あのホロライブで、やっぱり先輩方だったりとか、あと同期のみんなだったりとか、今後ライブするときにダンスをさ、ぐわってやる時に、この背景合うんじゃないかなと思って、もうホロリスだから、ホロめに使ってもらいたいがためにこのね、ステージを作らせていただきました。
so when doing Hololive live performances with seniors or gen-mates in the future, dancing dynamically against this background would fit well. Since I'm a fan, I had this stage made so they could use it for Holomem!
いや、かっこいいでしょこれ！めちゃくちゃかっこいい。落ち着くね、アンティーク調の、クロワになっているんですが、
Man, isn't this cool? Super cool. It's calming, with an antique-style decor...
そしてそれだけじゃないんです。ラストの1つ、
And that's not all. The very last one,
どどどどどどどどどどど！どうですかこれ！
ta-da-da-da-da-da! How is this?!
そう、バーの、バーステージといえばやっぱりね、ライブステージ！そう、ジャズなね、ライブをしたりだとか、こうオーケストラのライブをしたりだとかね、するとおしゃれなんじゃないかなっていうことで、この、バーステージ、ま、3パターンの楽しみ方がありますよというこでつくらせていただきました。
Right, a bar stage of course means a live stage! Doing jazz live shows or orchestral live shows would be stylish, so I had this bar stage made with three patterns of enjoyment in mind.
どうみんな？ちょっとみんなのコメントが見たいからじゃあちょっとステージに戻って、大丈夫かな？はい。
How is everyone? I want to see everyone's comments, so let's head back to the stage. Is that okay? Yes.
どうですかね、みなさん気に入っていただけた？すごいおしゃれ！いいね。絵のところを、
How is it, everyone? Did you like it? Super stylish! Nice. Over by the paintings...
ツーで写せそう！私がね、そら先輩のライブで壁面参加しましたけれども。そうだね、ライブツーで写せそうね。
Looks like you could project it in 2D! I participated on the wall in Sora-senpai's live, though. That's right, looks like we can project it in 2D live.
なんか今後あったら面白いよね。本てとましょみたいなで。
It'd be interesting if there's more in the future. Like it's actually the main show!
ということで、ここであのちょっと色々写真を撮っていこうかなと思うんですがな、なになに？ゲストが来てくれてるみたいなんんで、
So, I think I'll take various photos here, but wait, what's this? It seems a guest has come,
ちょっとゲスト呼びたいと思います。私もね、ゲスト誰なのか分からないんだけど、じゃあちょっと呼んでみますか。
so I'd like to call out the guest. I don't know who the guest is either, so let's call them out.
誰だ？
Who is it?
あら！あらららら！
Oh! Oh my goodness!
るいともさん！あ、るいともさんも3D化しちゃったみたいですね！
Ruitomo-san! Oh, Ruitomo-san has also been 3D-ified, it seems!
はい、ということで、お誕生日のとき6月11日のね生誕祭のときにデザインを公開したばかりなのに、
Yes, so, right after revealing the design during the June 11th birthday celebration,
もう3Dに、るいともさんなっちゃいました！というこで、るいともさんも含めてね、ちょっと写真も撮りたいなと思うんですが、
Ruitomo-san has already become 3D! So, including Ruitomo-san, I'd like to take some photos,
ちょっと、ソファ座ってもいいかな？ソファ座ります。よいしょ。
but can I sit on the sofa? I'll sit on the sofa. Heave-ho.
いやあ、いいですね。どうですか？ソファに合う？
Ah, this is nice. How is it? Does it match the sofa?
このソファもね、めちゃくちゃこだわって作ってもらったのよ。おしゃれでしょ？
This sofa was custom-made with so much attention to detail. Isn't it stylish?
あ、なんか生になってるね。
Ah, it's live now.
トゥルルン トゥルトゥン トゥルルン トゥルトゥン
Tururun turutun tururun turutun
はい。高嶺ルイの部屋始まりました！本日のゲストはルイ友さんです。
Yes! Takane Lui's Room has begun! Today's guest is Ruitomo-san.
それではね、ルイ友さん呼んで、あ、ちょっと...
Now then, let's call Ruitomo-san... Ah, wait...
大丈夫？なんか盛り上がってるルイ友さん、大丈夫？
Are you okay? Ruitomo-san seems super pumped, are you alright?
あ、ルイ友さんもね、座りたいか？じゃあ、ちょっと座る？
Ah, do you want to sit down too, Ruitomo-san? Then want to sit for a bit?
おひざに座ろうか。
Shall we sit on my lap?
最初に、えーじゃあ女の子の方。よいしょ。
First, um, the girl version. Heave-ho.
はい。
There you go.
えーと、はい。おひざに乗ってえらいね。
Um, yes. You're such a good girl sitting on my lap.
おいしょおいしょおいしょおいしょ、かわいい。
Heave-ho heave-ho, so cute.
かわいいな。今日は見に来てくれてありがとね。
So cute. Thanks for coming to watch today.
はい。で、ちょっと、じゃあ座っててもらって。
Right. Now, if you could just sit there for a moment.
男の子のルイ友さん、おいで。よいしょ。
Boy Ruitomo-san, come here. Heave-ho.
はい。どう？私のひざの座り心地はどうだい？
There. How is it? How does my lap feel to sit on?
ちょっとジタバタしないの。ちょっとジタバタする悪い子は、お仕置きがあるよ。大丈夫？
Now, don't squirm around. Bad kids who squirm get punished, you know. Are you okay?
ちょっとジタバタしない！もみもみじゃないのよ。あーかわいいかわいい。ねえ。
Don't squirm! No kneading around. Ah, so cute, so cute. Right?
というわけでさ、一緒に座って、
So, sitting together like this,
あ、どうですか？
Ah, how is it?
あ、一緒に座れたね。おっ。
Ah, we were able to sit together. Oh.
フークアイモードになった。おっ！え、嘘！君たちもフークアイモードになるだとう？
They went into hook-eye mode. Oh! Wait, really? You guys turn into hook-eye mode too?
じゃあおソロだ。おソロでじゃあ、はい、チーズ。
Then we match. Matching, so, ready, cheese.
どうかな？写真撮れた？うまく。
How is it? Were you able to take a good photo?
じゃあね、先ほどなんかコメントにもあった、ちょっとお仕置きをしてくださいていう人が結構多いみたいなので、
Now then, it seems a lot of people in the comments earlier asked me to give them some punishment,
じゃあ、お仕置き、しょうがないからしてあげようかな。
so I suppose I have no choice but to punish you.
ということでさっき悪さをしたルイ友はどっちだ？どっちだ？
So, which Ruitomo was the bad one earlier? Which one?
おい、出てきなさい。あ、ストップ向いてんじゃないよストップ！
Hey, come on out. Ah, don't look away, stop!
こっちに来なさい。こっちにほい、おいで。
Come over here. Over here, hey, come on.
うんうんじゃないのよ。
Don't give me that "yes, yes" attitude.
はい、お、来なさい、来なさい。
Right, oh, come here, come here.
じゃあね、ちょっと、女の子には痛いぞ、お尻から。
Now, this might hurt the girl, right on the bottom.
よし、いくぞ。えい！痛いか？
Alright, here we go. Hey! Does it hurt?
さっきはよくももみもみしやがって！おい！えい！
You had a lot of nerve kneading me earlier! Hey! Take that!
えい！ちょっと、なんか優しい、優しい感じにしちゃったけど、もっと欲しいのかい？
Hey! I made it kind of gentle and soft, but do you want more?
なんか喜んでる、喜んでるんだけど、大丈夫？
You look happy, you're actually happy about this, are you alright?
じゃあ、ちょっと画面の向こうのみんなにもお仕置きしちゃおうかな？
Shall I punish everyone on the other side of the screen too?
えい！なんか、エロいこと考えて、賢者とか言って、サジェストを荒らしたの誰だ、どこのドイツなんだよ！
Take that! Who was it, which one of you perverts was thinking lewd things and messing up the search suggestions with "sage time"!
こらこらこらこらこら！
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
早く3Dって、つぶやいて、サジェストを3Dまみれにしろ！おいおいおいおい！
Hurry up and tweet "3D" and flood the search suggestions with 3D! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
ということでね、なんかトレンド、トレンド、結構、いい感じのトレンドになったみたいなんですね。
So it seems like it became a pretty good trend on Twitter.
あ、いち！ありがとうございます！これで、サジェスト、賢者なくなるよね。
Ah, one! Thank you very much! With this, "sage" will disappear from the suggestions, right?
まあね、ちょっとわか、賢者って何のことやねんって方はね、ぜひぜひ、あの切り抜きとかも回ってますのでね、見ていただければなと思います。
Well, for those who are wondering what "sage" refers to, please do check out the clip compilations going around.
ということで、今度はステージの方に行きましょうか。
So, shall we head over to the stage area next?
ステージの方に、レッツゴー！
To the stage area, let's go!
あ、こっちか。
Ah, this way.
うわー、と、いうことでこのステージ、いかがですか？結構広々としてるでしょ？さっき見た感じだとちょっと狭いのかなって思った人もいるかもしれないですが、
Whoa! So, how do you like this stage? Quite spacious, right? Some of you might have thought it looked a bit cramped from earlier,
そう、広いんですよ！
but it's actually really roomy!
ということでここでね、ちょっとみんなにサービスを、私のさ、ちょっとかわいいお顔を見てほしくて、
So for everyone here, as a treat, I want you to see my cute face up close,
ちょっとガチ恋距離にしても大丈夫？ガチ恋距離。
so is it okay if I get into "serious crush" close-up range? Serious crush range.
えっと、ど、ど、どう、どう？この、このカメラで行く？
Um, h-how is this? Shall we go with this camera?
さっきの、なんかガチ恋カメラないかな？
Is there that "serious love" camera from earlier?
さっきのありますかね？
Is there one from earlier?
はい。
Yes.
ちょっとね、待っていただければ
If you wait just a moment,
とっても可愛い、もう映えな写真が撮れるみたいなので
you can take super cute, photogenic pictures, so...
待っていきましょう、みんな。
Let's wait. Everyone,
何々？「助かる」「美しい」「可愛い」、そうでしょう？
what's this? "Lifesaver," "Gorgeous," "Cute," right?
あ、カメラいけるみたいなので、
Oh, it looks like the camera works, so—
よし、ガチ恋距離。
Alright, "serious love" distance.
どうですか？
How is it?
ん？可愛いしょ？
Hm? Cute, right?
はい。うんうんうん、なんかみんな満足してくれてる？
Yeah. Mm-hmm. Are you guys all satisfied?
はい。え、このカメラマジで盛れる！
Yeah. Wow, this camera makes me look amazing!
いや、すでにさ、可愛いんだけどさ、なんか1.5割増しで可愛くない？
I mean, I'm already cute, but isn't it like 150% cuter?
どうですかね？いっぱいいっぱい写真撮れた？
How was it? Were you able to take lots of pictures?
ありがとうございます。綺麗。可愛い。
Thank you. Pretty. Cute.
ありがとう！めちゃくちゃ嬉しい。
Thank you! I'm super happy.
ということで、ガチ恋距離もね、終わったところで
And with that, "serious love" distance has come to an end,
何やら？あれ？なんかこのステージで何をするのかって言いますと、
and what's this? Huh? If you're wondering what we're going to do on this stage,
この配信でね、あのサムネにも書いてありました、重大告知をしたいなって思うんですけれども、
in this stream, as it was written on the thumbnail, I'd like to make a major announcement, but...
なんか、ね、普通に重大告知させてくれたらいいのにさ、なんかこの発表をかけて
I mean, it'd be nice if you just let me make the major announcement normally, but it seems we have to
企画にね挑戦しないといけないらしくて、まあ、その企画ちょっと私腑に落ちないんだけど
take on a challenge for this announcement, and well, I'm not really convinced by this challenge,
じゃあ、ちょっと企画め、ちょっと言わせていただきます。
so let me announce the challenge.
その企画は、
That challenge is...
全力ジェスチャーゲーム！
The Full-Force Gesture Game!
なんでジェスチャーゲームしなきゃいけないんだ？はい、ということで、
Why do I have to do a gesture game? Anyway,
これからね、私ま、私にねジェスチャーのお題が5問出されるみたいです。5問。
from now on, it seems I'll be given 5 gesture prompts. 5 prompts.
で、そのお題に対して30秒間で私が全力でもこの3D手に入れた3Dをね駆使して、もう全力で、全力でジェスチャーをして、
And for each prompt, I have 30 seconds to make full use of this 3D body I've acquired, and do my absolute best gestures with all my might!
で、これから呼ぶスケットが5問中3問答えてくれたらクリアで告知することができると、普通に告知させてくれよ。
And if the helpers I'm about to call can answer 3 out of 5, it's clear and I can make the announcement—just let me announce it normally!
っていうなんかけチャレンジがあるので、まあ、ちょっと告知できないのは残念なのでね、告知をかけて全力ジェスチャーをして行きたいと思います。
Since there's this challenge, and it'd be a shame not to be able to make the announcement, I'm going to do my best with full-force gestures for the announcement.
はい。ということで、私も頑張るんだけど、やっぱりさ、答えてくれるスケットが誰かに寄りますよね。ねえ。
Right. So, I'll do my best too, but of course, whether they can answer depends on who the helper is, right? Right.
ま、ルイ友さんだったら私のことさ分かってくれてるんじゃないかなと思うので、ルイ友さんだったらいいなって言ったらルイ友さんはダメらしくて、
I thought Ruitomos would understand me best, so I said it'd be great if it was Ruitomos, but apparently Ruitomos aren't allowed,
なので、まあ私のことを知っている、もう知り尽くしてるメンバーと言えば、そう、ホロックスのメンバーですね。
so when it comes to members who know me inside and out, well, that would be the HoloX members!
なので、呼びたいと思います協力なスケットカモン！
So, I'd like to call upon our trusty helpers—come on!
どうもどうもどうもどうもどうもどうも！あ、こんばんは。あ、こんばんは、ホロックスのメンバー。あれ？
Hello, hello, hello! Ah, good evening. Ah, good evening, HoloX members. Wait?
なんか、あれ？もう1人足りないけど、あ、ちょ、1人足りな、
Wait, huh? One person is missing, ah, wait, one person is—
「気のせいです」あ、気のせい？あ、じゃあ1人ずつ挨拶してもってもいいかな？
"It's just your imagination." Ah, my imagination? Well then, would you mind greeting one by one?
「側頭クセを」「おしおき食らわせです」どういうことだ？
"Sokutou kuse o" "Give them punishment" What does that even mean?
後でピシピシお仕置きしてあげるよ。気持ちいい！
I'll give you a good spanking later. That feels great!
はい。じゃあ、あのちゃんと頑張って答えてね。「任せろ」「うん、頼むよ」「はい。じゃあ小夜」
Right. So, do your best to answer properly. "Leave it to me." "Yeah, count on you." "Okay, then Sayo—"
「はーい、ことよー！ライブ直前のホロックスの頭脳発揮公演だよ！惜しい！おしいきーで！」
"Haaai, got it! It's HoloX's brainpower showcase right before the live! So close! Oshi-ki-de!"
あ、なんか今日、今日がお披露めななのに、明日がお披露めだって
Ah, somehow today, even though today is the unveiling, it turns out tomorrow is the unveiling—
なんか告知した人がいるみたいな、お仕置きが必要かな？「あ、あ、えでも、鞭で叩いてくれるなら、それはちょっと嬉しいかも」
It seems someone leaked the announcement, so maybe punishment is in order? "Ah, ah, well, if you whip me, I might actually be a little happy."
じゃあ後でピシピシとね、お尻を、「おしりより先にやってまうっちゃもんね」
Then later with smacks, your butt— "You're doing it before the butt!"
叩いてやりたいなと思うんですけど、この中で、まあ、私はねこの3人の中の一番変態なんじゃないかって思っている。はい、いろは。
I'd love to spank it, but among these three, I think I might be the biggest pervert. Yes, Iroha.
「おーい、こら！とゆーわけで、ホロライブ6期生の頭脳派吸血鬼、風真いろはでござるー！」
"Hey, come on! And with that, I am Kazama Iroha, Hololive 6th Generation's brain-type vampire!"
別に届いてほしいとか言わないでござるけど、「これがいいんだろ！これが！」
Not that I'm saying I want it to reach you, but "This is what you want, right! This!"
いや、そうゆうやつだったんだ。
Right, it was that kind of guy.
いやいや、待って待って！
Yorun - Koyorun! Wait, wait!
はい。
Right.
あれ、だから一人足りなくない?
Wait, doesn't that mean someone's missing?
ねえ、寝ぼけてるとかじゃないよね?
You're not sleeping through this, are you?
ちゃんと見てくれてるよね、私のLIVEで。
You're watching over our hearts, right?
なんか一人足りなくなったって言うのやめてよ。
Hey, stop saying things like someone's missing!
ということで、じゃあさ...
With that said, so...
三人とも、自信のほど、自信のほど、どうですか?
How confident are you three?
いや、もう任せて。
Well, leave it to us!
ねえ。
Right.
お前のことなら何でもわかるよ。
If it's about you, I'd understand no matter what.
まあ、何千年寄り添いましたからね、わかってくれなきゃ困っちゃうんですけどね。
We've stayed by your side for thousands of years, so you have to understand us!
何千年。やんぞ。何年、やってくんな。
Thousands of years. Do it, then.
あ、でも、本当にね、正解しないと...
And really, if you don't get this right...
実 はこのメンバーの中の重大告知もあるので、ぜひぜひ頑張っていただかないと困るんですよ。
There are actually some major disclosures about this member hidden inside, so you really have to do your best!
やるぞ。やるぞ。
We'll do it.
頑張ろう。頑張ってくだしゃい。頑張るでござるよ。
Do your best. Let's do our best.
じゃあ、早速始めましょうか。
So, let's start right away.
はい。
Right.
Yes.
お題は、私と今ね、見てくださっている配信の、配信を見てくださっている方々だけにでます。ロックスメンバーにはでません。
The prompt is only for me and the stream viewers watching right now. It's not for the Hohlolics members.
配信閉じる、閉じるぞ。閉じる開けろ。閉じる開けろ。
So close the stream! Close it! Close it!
それでは、準備はいいかな?
So, is preparation good?
はーい。
Okay!
いつでもこいよ。
Come on!
ということで、電力ジェスチャー1問目、スタート！
So, Power Gesture #1, start!
行くぜ。
Let's go.
あ、こいつ始まるんや。あ、始まってる。
Oh, this one's starting. Oh, it's starting.
お?え?なに?めポーズ?
What? What? What is this pose?
アイドル?アイドルじゃない。え?女幹部?
Idle? Idle, no, woman...
自分?わかる?え?
Self? What?
女?女...
Woman? Woman...
女?女幹部?女幹部?
Woman, woman, woman executive!
あー、正解！すごい！やったー！
Ah, correct! Amazing!
天才！
Genius!
え、30秒以内だったよね?
It was within 30 seconds, right?
うん。
Yes.
え、え、なんでわかったの今ので?
Wait, how did you figure that out from just now?
え、いやなんか、あの自分自分っててたから、うーんって思ってあのいつも自己紹介の時にやるフォンガがあったから、女幹部だと思って...
Well, when you did "self-self," I thought "hm" and then remembered your usual self-introduction pose, "Honga," so I figured "Ah, woman executive" and...
いや、さすがだ！天才でござるな。
Yeah, you're a genius!
いや、こういう音ね、いろはもちょ、惜しいところまで行ってたんだけどね。
Yeah, Iroha and I went quite close to the answer, though.
そうだね。気づかなかったね。
That's right, we almost got it.
ねえ。
Right?
ま、ルイねえといえば女幹部でござるからな。
Well, Louie-nee is a woman executive, after all.
ねえ、そうだよ。
That's right.
じゃあ、この調子で2問目いけるか?
Then, can we do the second one with this momentum?
オッケー、任せてでござるよ。
Okay, leave it to us!
順調だからね、これでストレートがしよう。
It's going well, so let's make this one straightforward.
うえなんか負けるな。
Let's see if we lose to Lui-nee.
負けねえ。行くぞ、2問目、スタート！
Lose? Let's go! Question 2, start!
酔っ払い！
Drunk!
あ、正解！すごい！すごい！
Ah, correct! Amazing!
やったー！
Yay!
えー！よくわかったね！
Hey, you figured it out!
なんか酔ってる感じがした。
I felt like you were getting drunk.
だってもっと綺麗に振っててから、ベルリンとかなんかと思ってたんだけど、思ってたらなんか。
I thought you were swinging around too cleanly, so I wondered if it was Berlin or something, but then you started staggering.
思いのほか綺麗にちょっと酔けちゃったから。
I got a little too excited because I was too clean.
さすがね、綺麗でござるな。
Well, as expected, you're clean.
動きがね、ちょっと綺麗すぎるんだな。
Your movements were just too clean.
いや、やっぱり私、こういうジェスチャーゲームとか得意なのかもしれない。
Yeah, maybe I'm good at gesture games.
うん、私の、理解力かも知れん。
Or maybe it's your comprehension ability.
確かにね。動きめっちゃ綺麗だからな。
True. Your movements are super clean, after all.
ねえ、そうなんでござる。花があるんでござる。
That's right. And there are flowers, too!
嬉しい！
Yay!
じゃあ、もう...
So, are we...
あれ?3問、あれ?3問正解したらいいみたいだから、次ね。
If we get the third one right, that's it?
え、ちょっと。二人とも、二人とも次答えて、二人とも。え、答えて。え、頑張って、頑張って。
Come on, both of you, answer the next one correctly! Let's do your best!
頑張って！
Do your best!
こよりといろは、行くよ！
Koyori and Iroha, let's go!
行くで！
Let's go!
3問目、スタート！
Question 3, start!
コンコン！
Con-con!
オイル！二人とも頑張れ！
Oil! Both of you, do your best!
オイルじゃないの?え?何?会社?
It's not oil! What? Company?
社会?
Society?
チャット?チャット?
Chat? Chat, chat?
なんだ?海外じゃないの?りおん?お仕事?ビジネスマンとか?
What? That's not it? Office worker?
え?何?なんでわからないの?え?
What? Why didn't you get that?
なんか、シマウマのってわかった。シマってなんか出してヒューヒューヒュってしてるのでわかった。
I understood it when you simulated typing, and then you made a "shh" gesture and typed with "hew-hew-hew." I understood!
これ、私もう絶対ダメだと思ってた。
I thought for sure that was impossible.
え、ちょっと。諦めるの早すぎでしょ。それを舐めすぎだよ。
I mean, giving up that easily is underestimating us too much!
ストレートで成功！
Straight success!
すごい！ナイスー！
That's amazing!
やったー！
Yay!
いや、もう4問目、5問目やらなくて済んだわ、ありがとう！
Well, we didn't have to do the 4th and 5th questions, but thank you!
なんだよ！
What is that?
ということで、じゃあね、告知、ご褒美の告知タイムに行きましょうか。
So, let's move on to the prize notification time.
はい。
Yes.
ということで、まずはちょっとみんなにもね、言ってもらって。
So, first, let everyone say a few words.
さあ、おさらいです。
Now, let's do a review.
ドン！
Bam!
はい、鷹嶺ルイの6月11日に発売しました
Right, Takane Lui's birthday commemoration goods
誕生日記念のグッズがまだまだ発売中でございます。
released on June 11th, are still on sale.
フルセットには、あ、今セットでしょ？
The full set includes—ah, the full set right?
フルセットには私の直筆サインがついていまして、あの、数量限定などでは
The full set comes with my handwritten autograph, and since it's not limited in quantity,
ありませんので、ぜひぜひね、7月入ってから、ちょ、今日はのお金がちょっとやばい
so please, once July starts—wait, if you're like "I'm running low on money today",
みたいなね、方に、関しましては7月に入ってからでも全然大丈夫なので、あの、よかったら
it's completely fine even after July starts, so um, if you'd like,
買っていただければなと
I hope you'll purchase it.
思いいます。はい、ラインナップはこちら。
Yes, here is the lineup.
いや、どうですか？ドン、ドン、ドン、はい、
Well, what do you think? Bam, bam, bam, yes,
ワイングラス欲しいね！
I want that wine glass!
晩酌配信にもいいし、しかもお酒で飲めない方はなんか小物入れとかにもできるおしゃれなワイングラスにしてみたので、ね。
It's great for drinking streams, and for those who can't drink, I made it a stylish wine glass that can also be used as a trinket holder.
あとは、まあ、がんもですね、結構人気ながんもキーホルダーもね、一緒にがんも連れて歩けるので、よかったら買っていただけたらなと思います。
And then, well, Gamo—the quite popular Gamo keychain too, you can walk around with Gamo, so I hope you'll buy it.
あと、記念ボイスはね、私がシナリオを担当させていただきましたので、よかったら聞いてください！
Also, for the commemoration voice, I was in charge of the scenario, so please listen to it!
どんなん？デートやん実質。デートだよ。
What's it like? It's basically a date. It's a date!
よかったらあとでちょっと私から聞いて。や、飲んでも大丈夫で
If you'd like, I'll give it to you later, so listen. No, it's totally fine to drink—
あ、買うの？買ってくれんの？
Ah, you're buying it? You'll buy it for me?
いや、それは嬉しいけど。
Well, I'd be happy, but...
よし、じゃあ、続いては、
Alright, then, next is...
誰の告知だ？ドン！
Whose announcement is this? Bam!
はい、ラプラス・ダークネスが重大告知が明日19時にあるみたいですね。
Right, it seems Laplace Darkness has a major announcement stream tomorrow at 7 PM.
明日19時に重大告知私聞いてないんだけど。
Wait, major announcement tomorrow at 7 PM? I haven't even heard about it.
まあ、ありますね、これね。
Well, it exists, right here.
まあ、暇だったら見に来てください。
Well, if you're free, please come watch.
いや、みんな見に来るよきっと。
I'm sure everyone will come watch.
どんなこと告知するんだ？飲むんだろうね。
What kind of announcement is she making? Drinking, probably.
え、このシルエットはなに？もしかして新衣装？新衣装かな？
Eh, what's this silhouette? Could it be a new outfit? A new outfit maybe?
なんだろうね、なんかちょっと流れを理解しようとしたけど、
I wonder what it is. I tried to understand the flow, but...
あ、ちょっと、ちょっとやめましょうね。
Ah, let's, let's stop here.
はい、ということでみなさん6月22日明日ですね、明日の19時にラプラスのチャンネルで重大告知配信がありますのでぜひぜひ見に行ってください。
Right, so everyone, June 22nd—tomorrow, at 7 PM tomorrow, there will be a major announcement stream on Laplace's channel, so please go check it out.
よろしくお願いします！みんな見インるぞ。
Thank you! Everyone go watch.
はい、3人ともありがとう。ちょっと黒鳶は閉めといて。
Yes, thank you to all three. Kurotobi, close it up.
綺麗に締めとくね！ありがとう。
Wrap it up nicely! Thank you.
ということで3人でした！ありがとう。またね！見てるからね！
And that was the three of us! Thank you. See you! I'm watching!
ということで、重大告知の前に私、あのやり忘れたこと1つあって、これやらないと悔いが残るのでやってもいいですか？やっていいです？
Now, before the major announcement, there's one thing I forgot to do, and if I don't do this, I'll have regrets, so can I do it? Is it okay if I do?
えっと、私と言えば、そう、あのホロックスの女幹部なんですけれども、秘密海賊団のエロ女幹部でもあるので、あれをやっとかないとなっていうことでやらせていただければなと、思います。
Um, speaking of me, right, I'm the female executive of Holox, but I'm also the lewd female executive of the Secret Pirate Crew, so I have to do *that*, and that's why I'd like to do it.
いくぞ！アホイ！
Here we go! Ahoy!
え、ホロライブ6期生秘密海賊団エロ女幹部の鷹嶺ルイです！
Eh, I am Takane Lui, the lewd female executive of Hololive 6th Generation Secret Pirate Crew!
どう？よかった！
How was it? That's great!
最初にやろうと思ってたんだけどさ、緊張してちょっと飛んでしまって、やらせていただきました。どう、どう、どう、エロ、エロかった？
I was planning to do it first, but I got nervous and my mind went blank, so I went ahead and did it. How was it? Was it lewd?
はい、ということで、もういっか。はい、それでは、
Yes, so... that's enough. Right, then,
重大告知いきます！はい、ここから重大告知です。本日この配信終了後に、こちら、
Now for the major announcement! Yes, here is the major announcement. Today, right after this stream ends, this—
はい、先ほども歌わさせていただきました、「キミソラキセキ」がね、え、投稿されます。プレミア公開されます。
Yes, as I sang earlier, my cover of 'Kimi Sora Kiseki' will be posted—it will have a premiere release.
はい、この21時、ちょっとすぎかな、にプレミア公開されるのでぜひぜひ見に行ってください。
Yes, it will premiere around 21:00, just a bit after, so please definitely go check it out.
続いて、こちら！はい、本日23時から、
Next, this! Yes, starting at 23:00 today,
え、メンバー限定配信をさせていただきます。「おうち3D」でね、打ち上げ晩酌をやらせていただこうかなと思いますので、今日メンバーに入った方ぜひぜひ楽しみにしててください。
um, I will hold a membership-only stream. We'll be doing an after-party drinking stream in 'Home 3D', so if you joined as a member today, please look forward to it.
そしてそして、次が、待ちにまったあの発表です。ドン！
And then, next is the announcement we've all been waiting for. Bam!
はい、ということで、お誕生日のときにお話が、ありました！
Yes, so, news about my birthday was shared!
ヒーらぎ嫌い先生に書いていただきました、
Hirokigi Kirai-sensei wrote for me
オーバードというオリジナル曲が、
an original song called "Overd",
本日24時に各種音楽サイトで配信されます！わーー！
releasing on various music sites tonight at 24:00! Yay!
いやもうさ、かっこいい、かっこいいって好評で、
People have been saying it's so cool and awesome,
もう本当に嬉しいです。私もねめちゃくちゃ気に入ってる楽曲なので、
and I'm honestly so happy. It's a track I love dearly,
ぜひぜひみんなにもたくさん聴いてほしいなということで、3Dおめでとうっていう気持ちでね、
so I really want everyone to listen to it a lot. With the feeling of "Congrats on 3D,"
ぜひぜひ24時に買って頂ければなと思います。
please definitely buy it at 24:00!
そしてこのMVとあとあのフリ付けのね、TikTokなんかも後日投稿させていただきますので、楽しみに待っててくださーい。
And the MV and its choreography on TikTok will be posted later, so please look forward to it!
そして本日はこのオーバードを配信に先駆けて初披露させていただきます！イエーイ！
And today, we'll be premiering "Overd" right here before its release! Yay!
ということでオリジナル曲オーバードなんですけれども、
So, regarding the original song "Overd,"
この曲はね、あの女幹部の表向きの女幹部のお仕事とあと裏にある私の気持ちみたいな、
this song depicts the gap between a female executive's public duties
ちょっとそういったねギャップを描いてもらった闇の闇、ちょっとダークチックな歌詞になってますので、ぜひぜひ楽しんで聴いていただけたらなと思うんですが、
and my hidden feelings underneath—a bit dark and shadowy—so I hope you'll enjoy listening to it!
24時にね配信の、まあ、ちょっと音源とはこれから歌うのでね、違うのでそういったちょっと音源の聴き比べもねしてくださったら嬉しいです。
Since it releases at 24:00 and what I'll sing now is slightly different from the audio source, I'd be happy if you compare them.
ということで行きましょうか早速。はいということで、
So let's get right into it. Yes,
オリジナル曲オーバードぜひ聴いてください。
please enjoy my original song, "Overd."
四六時中 帰りの会で
Every single time at the wrap-up meeting
面倒くささを押し付けられている
Getting all the annoyances dumped on me
何から何まで
From this to that
私語は止めて まとめ役なら
Stop whispering, if you're the coordinator
聞くを上手にうなずき合ってる
Nodding along like a good listener
なかよしこよしで
All buddy-buddy,
さあだだだだ黙れ黙りたまえよ
Now shut up, shut the hell up!
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such strong words,
少しだけ静かにしてほしいね
So I want you to quiet down just a little.
ああ 私達大望へ
Ah, toward our grand ambition,
世界転覆 ヤーヤーヤー
World conquest, yay, yay, yay!
果たすその日まで
Until the day we achieve it,
煉々 煉獄 イエーイ イエーイ イエーイ
Burning purgatory, yeah, yeah, yeah!
あなたの周りも ヨールーヨー
All around you is yo, yo, yo!
下界征服 アレアレアー
Conquering the lower realm, ale, ale, a!
約束の地まで さあ掲げろ xx
To the promised land, raise it high xx!
転転 転覆 ヤーヤーヤー
Turning over, yay, yay, yay!
今日も議題 そっちのけだね
Ignoring the agenda again today,
嫌になるから
Because I hate this so much,
私一人でもやっておきますね
I'll just do it all by myself!
全て全て全て任せて
Leave everything, everything to me,
それをさせてよ大事なことなの
Let me do it, it's an important thing—
分かっているでしょ
You know that, right?
四六時中 帰りの会で
Every single time at the wrap-up meeting
面倒くさいまま
The annoyances remain,
今日も明日も過ぎていくのでしょう
And every day keeps passing on away.
花瓶に水をあげましょう
Let's water the flower vase,
時の中萎れたこと忘れていた
Forgotten wilting under the pressure of time.
さあ黙れ 黙りたまえよ
Now shut up, shut the hell up!
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such strong words,
少しだけ静かにしてほしいね
So I want you to quiet down just a little.
ああ 私達大望へ
Ah, toward our grand ambition,
今と未来 見たかったはずなのに
Wanting to see the present and future,
世界転覆 ヤーヤーヤー
World conquest, yay, yay, yay!
見えぬその日まで
Until the day we can't see anymore.
滔々 滔々 とえんえんえん
Endlessly, without end, end, end,
この世の理 ヨールーヨー
The rules of this world, yo, yo, yo!
今は潜伏 サササ
Now we lay low, low, low,
あなたの街中形作るは xさ
Bringing your town to life, it's x!
世界転覆 ヤーヤーヤー
World conquest, yay, yay, yay!
果たすその日まで
Until the day it comes true,
煉々 煉獄 イエーイ イエーイ イエーイ
Burning purgatory, yeah, yeah, yeah!
あなたの周りも ヨールーヨー
All around you is yo, yo, yo!
下界征服 アレアレアー
Conquering the lower realm, ale, ale, a!
約束の地まで さあ掲げろ xx
To the promised land, raise it high xx!
転転 転覆したら
Once we finish our conquest,
ビンテージのワインを開けましょう
Let's open up a bottle of vintage wine.
ここにひざまずけ！
Kneel before me!
はい、でステレオな現実も
Yes, and even a stereotypical reality...
一刀両断、手痛き傷
Cleaved in two, a painful wound
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし蝙蝠よ
Oh bat lost in endless reincarnation!
漆黒の翼でいざなわれ
Guided by jet-black wings,
我らエデンの星を滑るもの秘密結社
We who rule the star of Eden, Secret Society
ホロライブの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイ！
holoX's executive, Takane Lui!
いつも思うのは、不器用だってこと
What I always think is how clumsy you are.
人一倍努力をして、時には自分を犠牲にしてでも、
Working twice as hard as anyone, sacrificing yourself,
誰かのために頑張れるのが貴方のすごいところ。
and being able to work hard for others is your trait.
その優しさに私を含めた皆が支えられているし、
That kindness supports everyone, including me,
貴方自身も誰かの笑顔に安堵してると思う。
and you yourself find relief in someone's smile.
今日も自分の周りの人が少しでも幸せでよかったって。
Thinking, "I'm glad the people around me are happy."
でも、私はそんな貴方を見ていて不安になります。
But seeing you like that makes me worried.
いつも笑って、困ってる人には身親に寄り添い、
Always smiling, supporting those in trouble,
人のために怒ったり悲しんだりできる、頼れるルイ姉になってしまう貴方は、
becoming the dependable big sis Lui for others—
本当に無理をしてないですか？
are you really not overworking yourself?
誰かのために自分のやりたかったこと、言いたかった事、本当は我慢したくない事を飲み込み、押し殺してないかな？
Swallowing and hiding what you truly wanted to do or say?
貴方は自分の心を後回しに明るく振る舞うけど、本当はとても繊細で人の機微に聡く、抱え込みやすい事を知っています。
You act cheerful, but you tend to bottle things up.
無理をするなと言われても、無理してしまうのも知っています。だから変わってほしいなんて言わない。
I know you'll still push yourself. I won't ask you to change.
でも今日だけは、ありのままの貴方で楽しんでほしい。
But just for today, I want you to enjoy yourself.
誰かのためでなく、貴方だけの為に貴方自身を輝かせてほしい。
Not for someone else, but for your own sake.
貴方も同じアイドルなんだよ、遠慮なんてしないでいいんだよ。
You're an idol too, you don't need to hold back.
側で見てきたたくさんの努力たちは全て報われていいものだったから。
Because your efforts deserve to be rewarded.
だから今ここで私達に見せてほしい。貴方が本当に望む貴方を。
So show us right here—the you that you truly wish to be.
貴方の軌跡と貴方が描く未来を。
Your footprint and the future you draw.
クロエより
From Chloe
はい、クロエ、ありがとう！
Yes, Chloe, thank you!
いや、もう、泣きちまった。
Man, I went and cried.
いや、ちょっと、あの、スタッフさんにティッシュ持ってきてもらったんだけど、もう全然足りないんだよ、ティッシュ。本当にありがとう。うん。
I had the staff bring tissues, but it's not nearly enough.
もう私なんかね、アイドルなんてって自分でも思っていたんですが、やっぱり、あの、ホロライブに入ったからには歌って踊れるアーティスト、そしてアイドルになりたいなと思って、自信がついたときにはこの曲を歌おうって思っていました。
I wanted to become an idol, and decided to sing this song.
なので、ぜひ、あの、ホロのね、オリジナル曲今まで歌ってこなかったんですけども、初めて歌うならこの曲と決めていた曲、ぜひ聴いてください。
This is my first original song, so please listen to it.
いきます。キラメキライダー☆
Here we go. Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高の間 最高 の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
キラメキに乗っ て☆
Riding on the sparkle☆
（イエーイ）
(Yeah!)
覚えてるかな？
Do you remember?
最初の歌（懐かしいね）
Our first song, such a nostalgic memory.
私 声が震えていた（ほんの少し）
My voice was trembling, just a little bit.
あの日から続く未来は みんなと掴んだ今日日よ
The future since then is what we grasped together!
もっともっともっともっと加速するハート
Accelerating heart, ever faster and faster!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高な時間 最高な仲間とキラメキに乗って☆
With the best time and friends, riding on the glitter☆
（いぇーい）
(Yay!)
覚えてるかな？最初の歌
Do you remember? Our very first song
私 声が震えてた
My voice was trembling
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day
みんなで掴んだ今日だよ
Is today we grasped together with everyone
もっともっともっともっと加速するハート
More and more and more accelerating heart
（一緒に）行こうどこまでも
(Together) Let's go anywhere
（Are you ready?）準備はOK？
(Are you ready?) Are you ready?
ひらけ！！夢のトビラを
Open the door to our dreams!!
（いち に さん）
(One, two, three)
（キラメキラライダー☆）
(Kirameki Rider☆)
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高な時間 最高な仲間とここにいるよ
With the best time and friends, I'm here
見つけてくれたから
Because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here to see you, let's sing together
終わらないメロディ
A never-ending melody
キラメキ纏って☆
Wrapped in glitter☆
届いているかな？私の声
I wonder if my voice is reaching you?
届けたいのは君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
理想の遠さに悔しくて
Frustrated by how far my ideals are
みんなで泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together, didn't we?
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと全て抱きしめて
Embracing everything tighter and tighter
（一緒に）いこうどこまでも
(Together) Let's go anywhere
（Are you ready?）準備はOK！
(Are you ready?) We're all set, okay!
すすめ！！希望の道を
Advance!! Along the road of hope
（いち に さん）
(One, two, three)
（キラメキラライダー☆）
(Kirameki Rider☆)
好きな気持ちカラフルに奏でたいんだ
I want to play my favorite feelings colorfully
最高な場所 最高なみんなとここにいるよ
In the best place, with the best people, I'm right here
幻なんかじゃない
This is no illusion
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart can be dyed with happiness
重ねてくハーモニー キラメキ纏って☆
Layering our harmonies, wrapped in glitter☆
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing
そんな願いわがままでもいいですか？
Is it okay if such a wish is a bit selfish?
だって楽しくて！もうとまらない！！
Because it's so much fun! I can't stop anymore!!
輝くステージで もっともっと！！（お願い）ずっと！！
On this shining stage, more and more!! (Please) forever!!
（うー） （いぇーい）
(Woo) (Yay)
嬉しい楽しい愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Words like happy, joyful, or lovely aren't enough
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, I still have worries, but
ここにいるよ 私 ここにいるよ
I'm right here, I am right here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Gazing at the same world as you
（いくよ！）
(Let's go!)
（キラメキラライダー☆）
(Kirameki Rider☆)
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高な時間 最高な仲間とここにいるよ
With the best time and friends, I'm here
見つけてくれたから
Because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう（せーの）
I came here to see you, let's sing together (Ready, go)
終わらないメロディ キラメキに乗って☆
A never-ending melody, riding on the glitter☆
キラメキ纏って☆
Wrapped in glitter☆
このステージでこの歌を歌えて本当に幸せです
I am truly happy to sing this song on this stage
私もアイドルとして認めてくれますか？
Will you accept me as an idol too?
嬉しい楽しい愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Words like happy, joyful, or lovely aren't enough
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, I still have worries, but
ここにいるよ 私 ここにいるよ
I'm right here, I am right here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Gazing at the same world as you
（いくよ！）
(Let's go!)
（キラメキラライダー☆）
(Kirameki Rider☆)
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo!
最高な時間 最高な仲間とここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
With the best time and friends, I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう（せーの）
I came here to see you, let's sing together (Ready, go)
終わらないメロディ キラメキに乗って☆
A never-ending melody, riding on the glitter☆
キラメキ纏って☆
Wrapped in glitter☆
今日は、観に来てくれて本当にありがとう♡ 私が「アイドル」なんて…って自分で思っていて自信なかったケド、今なら胸を張れているかな！？
Thank you so much for coming today♡ I used to doubt myself, thinking 'Me, an idol...?' But can I hold my head high now!?
何事もあきらめなかった私がもう一度夢を追いかけたい！！と思ったのはホロライブそしてルイさんのおかげです！！
Wanting to chase my dreams once more as someone who never gave up on anything is thanks to Hololive and Lui-san!!
これからも全力で頑張るからついて来てね☆
I'll keep doing my absolute best, so please keep following me☆
鷹嶺ルイ 3D お披露目
Takane Lui 3D Reveal